let's born the throne awaits a few ones
of a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time the lion under me
Wow their mother will be fine
the children grow learn what's right
leaders of the freedom fight they seek
their mother she knows they do
will the prophecy come true
Brown
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow their mother will
be found Sonic Underground let's board
the throne awaits a seal wands of a
deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time
the lying waste I can't
we made
while their mother will be fine
the children grow learn what's right
leaders of the freedom fight they seek
their mother she knows they do is it
time
well the prophecy come true saya
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made about them
we'll be found Sonic Underground let's
board the throne awaits a seer warns of
a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time
the lying waste I can do
they may
while their mother will be found
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom phase they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time and she
will the prophecy come true
Sonique under Prime
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow their mother
Sonic Underground let's board the throne
awaits a few ones of a deadly fate give
up your children separate by your time
lying waste I can do
they may
now their mother will be fine
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time
will the prophecy come true
you can
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow them
we'll be bound Sonic Underground let's
board the throne awaits a few ones of a
deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time the lion way
Underground they made a bow their mother
will
bro learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time and she
will the pop machine come true
you can't
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow their mother will
be found Sonic Underground born the
throne awaits a seer warns of a deadly
fate give up your children separate by
your time lying waste I can Deborah
crowd
Wow their mother will be bow
the children grow learn what's right
leaders her the freedom fight they seek
their mother she knows they do is it
time it's the only
well the prophecy come true
saya
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made about their mother will
be found
let's board the throne awaits a CEO ones
of a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time the lion weighs I
can do
they made a bow their mother will be
fine
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time
will the publish she come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow their mother will
be found Sonic Underground let's board
the throne awaits a seer warns of a
deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time fly away
Underground
they made a bow their mother will be
fine
the children grow learn what's right
leaders of the freedom fight they seek
their mother she knows they do is it
time and she
you will the Papa see come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made about
will be found
let's board the throne awaits a CEO ones
of a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time the lion way
second Debra
they made a bow their mother will be
found
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom
born is thrown away I feel
sadly children
I can't
Wow
we'll be fine
learn what's right leaders her the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time
the prophecy come true
I don't actually I have to wait to add
too soon seal their thing they made
well be bombs on Underground the freedom
fight they seek their mother she knows
they do is it time
well the Papa see come true
saya
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow them
we'll be found Sonic Underground